Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

This Privacy Policy has been created to allow you, the user/visitor, to better understand how the data we collect is used on our website, vgy.me.

#### **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?**

We collect IP addresses and what pages/uploads a user has visited. The purpose of this is to understand where most of our traffic comes from so we can provide a better service in terms of speed, performance and loading times.

#### **When do we collect information?**

We collect information when you register as a user on our website, where we ask for a username and e-mail address.

We collect feedback/suggestions which can help improve the website for all.

Whenever you visit a page on our website, or when you view an upload, either from our website directly or from a 3rd party (such as a hotlinked image on a forum).

#### **How do we use your information?**

The information is used solely to improve vgy.me, it is never sold or given to 3rd party providers:

* If you register as a user on our website, we ask for your e-mail address, for the purpose of resetting your password if you have forgotten it. You will also receive an e-mail requesting you to activate your account. This is so we can be sure if you need to reset your password, a new password can be sent to you via e-mail securely.
* In some cases, we may use your e-mail address to check against logs with our mail service - this is usually only the case when a user hasn't received their activation/password reset e-mail. We can check to see why the e-mail wasn't sent and let the user know.
* To improve our website in order to better serve you.
* To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries), after which any trace of communication is deleted.
* When moderating our site, we may use your information to link to other pieces of information, such as uploads. This is only if a user/IP address has been caught violating our Terms of Service.
* We never add you to a mailing list upon registering to our website, we never send e-mails for marketing purposes.

#### **How do we protect your information?**

Nobody else has access to your information other than authorised server and site administrators. None of your personal information is displayed publicly on the website, your information can only be seen if you are logged in.

We do occasional audits of our site and server security, as well as keeping software as up to date as possible, to ensure any vulnerabilities have been patched.

#### **Do we use 'cookies'?**

We use cookies to provide a better service to you, to allow your browser to remember your preferences for our website. Cookies are also used to store data which link to your account in order to keep you logged in whilst you use the user-only features. Personal information is never stored in these cookies.

We don't track you through cookies through our site or other websites. It is solely for your browser(s) to "remember" your login, but we do encourage our users to always logout when they are done using our website.

Our site may contain cookies for 3rd party services, such as our ad placements. These are out of our control and done by the advertisement provider.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

#### **If users disable cookies in their browser:**

By turning cookies off, you may not be able to allow your browser to "remember your login" if you use the "Remember Me" option when logging in.

#### **Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

#### **Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### **Removal of your information:**

You may request to have any information stored about you on our servers permanently deleted. Please contact us [here](https://vgy.me/contact-us/general-enquiries) requesting it. We are unable to remove any information that are stored with 3rd party services that we use. You would need to get in contact with them about removal of personal information.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

* On our Privacy Policy Page

Can change your personal information:

* By logging in to your account

#### **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using [this page](https://vgy.me/contact-us/general-enquiries).

Long story short...
===================

We only use your personal information to moderate the website, to remove content that violates our Terms of Service and to ban users who also violate the Terms of Service. Sending of e-mail is triggered by you, the user, when resetting your password or when registering an account with us, where you will receive an activation link via e-mail. We don't send you e-mails for any other reason.

Your IP address is used for moderation to link uploads to the same IP address (we occasionally get users who spam our uploader with hundreds, sometimes thousands of uploads). IP addresses are also logged for us to understand where most of our traffic comes from, so we can provide a better service.

3rd party services who use cookies to store data about your visit is not controlled by us.

If you don't like your information on our site, let us know - we'll get rid of it.

Last Edited on 24th May 2018.

Copyright © vgy.me 2024
